pizzagogo.co.uk 2019-06-03

# Privacy Statement | Pizza GoGo

Welcome to Pizza GoGo's privacy policy. We respect the privacy of all visitors to our website, mobile app and stores. We are committed to protecting your personal data. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement or have any questions regarding your personal data, please contact our data protection officer by emailing: data@pizzagogo.net

Last modified: May 2018

* * *

**BY USING THIS WEBSITE YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CONTAINED IN THIS POLICY.**

* * *

## Introduction

Pizza GoGo Limited cares about your privacy. For this reason, we collect and use personal data only as it might be needed for us to provide to you our website platform (the "Website"), mobile application (the "App"), and business services including the sale of products (collectively, our "Services"). The Services are operated by Pizza GoGo Limited ("Pizza GoGo", the "Company", "we" or "us") for customers of the Services ("You"). 

If at any time you have questions about our practices or any of your rights described below, you may reach our Data Protection Officer ("DPO") and our dedicated team by contacting us at data@pizzagogo.net. This Email inbox is actively monitored and managed so that we can deliver an experience that you can confidently trust. 

## Who are we?

Pizza GoGo Limited is a business registered in England & Wales with company number 03104628. Our head office address is Unit 6 Teakcroft Fairview Industrial Park, Marsh Way, Rainham, Essex, RM13 8UH. 

## What information do we collect?

We collect personal data whenever you place an order with us via our website, on-line, phone and collection orders. We need this data to be able to fulfil your order, for example, your address and phone number when we need to deliver your order or should there be a problem with your order and we need to contact you. 

The data we collect and store is your postal address, email, telephone number and date of birth along with details of products you have ordered. Debit and Credit card details are never stored by us. We offer a service to place a token on your card details to allow for easy ordering in the future, however we do not have any access to your card number, expiry date or CVV number. This information is handled and protected by Globalpay. 

We may request personal data from publicly available sources and/or from third party data vendors. If we do this, we will ensure that the data provided has been collected and shared with us only if the GDPR regulations and guidelines have been followed when collecting that data. 

When you interact with us through our Services, we may collect information from you, as further described below: 

**a. Information you provide:** We collect information from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you register for access to our Services or use certain Services. Information we collect may include but not be limited to real name, email address, address, mobile phone number, date of birth, and any other information you upload to our Website or App. 

**b. Automatically collected information:** When you interact with us, we receive and store certain information such as an IP address, device ID, and your activities within the Services. Logging when you access the Services and from where, allows us to better understand our users and keep your account and information safe. 

**c. Aggregated information:** In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve our customers of the Services, we may conduct research on our customer demographics, interests and behaviour based on the information collected. We may also disclose aggregated and anonymized user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

**d. Cookies:** Like almost all online websites we employ cookies and similar technologies to keep track of your local device's settings and which account you are logged into. See below section "Cookies" for more. In addition to Cookies we may also use web beacons and single pixel gifs to log Email opens.  
See our Cookies Policy for more information. 

**e. Cookies (third party):** We use third party web site analytic tools such as Google Analytics on our Website that employ cookies to collect certain information concerning your use of our Services. However, you can disable cookies by changing your browser settings. Further information about the procedure to follow in order to disable cookies can be found on your Internet browser provider's website via your help screen.  
We use IP Anonymization on Google Analytics.  
See our Cookies Policy for more information. 

## Cookies

Please view our separate Cookies Policy. 

We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue without changing your settings, we'll assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on the services run by Pizza GoGo Limited. 

Currently cookies are used on our Services to identify you for usability purposes. These in no way track your movement around the Services or record any information about you. They are used specifically for identifying if you have used the site before, welcoming you as a returning user, and offering to show you your last order with Pizza GoGo. 

## Why do we process your personal data & how will it be used

We need to process and hold your personal data to be able to fulfil your orders and for when there is a problem with your order and we need to contact you.  
We also need to process your personal data for delivering, improving, updating, and enhancing the Services we provide to you.  
We strongly believe in both minimising the data we collect and limiting its use and purpose to only that (1) for which we have been given permission, (2) as necessary to deliver the Services you purchase or interact with, or (3) as we might be required or permitted for legal compliance or other lawful purposes. 

The purpose of collecting and storing your data is so that we can provide our goods and Services to you as well administrative purposes should you need to contact us regarding a past, present or future order. We also use this date, where you have agreed for us to do so, to send you marketing information. 

We use the information you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide information for a certain reason, we may use the information in connection with the reason for which it was provided. 

## Our legal basis for processing your personal data.

**a. Contractual necessity - Providing you with our Services:** We handle personal data on this basis to create your account and provide our Services, including delivery of products. 

**b. Legitimate interests:** We process your personal data on the basis of legitimate interests in ways that are not overridden by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of individuals. Including: 

  * Providing a safe and secure Website
  * Marketing - sending Emails to inform you of features or offers
  * Protecting our users, servers, and services
  * Analysing and improving our Services to you
  * Processing legal requirements

**c. Consent:** Handling data freely given by clear affirmative action. You have a right to withdraw consent, which must be brought to our attention. See below "Understanding your rights". 

## Our disclosure of your information

We will never disclose your information unlawfully. Pizza GoGo is not in the business of selling your data. There are however some circumstances in which we may share your information with certain third parties, as set forth below: 

**a. Delivering your order:** Products you order through our Services will be sent to your chosen store for fulfilment. These stores may or may not be run by Pizza GoGo Limited.   
Stores, and their drivers, need your name, address, and phone number to deliver your order and contact you if there is a problem. 

**b. Business transfers:** As our business grows we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of our take over, merger, corporate sale, reorganization, bankruptcy or similar, your information may be part of the transferred assets. 

**c. Legal requirements:** We may disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company or Related Companies, (iii) protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. 

**d. Google Analytics:** We utilize Google Analytics for website visitor tracking and analysis.   
We use [IP Anonymization](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en) on Google Analytics. 

**e. Trusted third parties:** See below "Sharing your personal data with trusted third parties". 

## Sharing your personal data with trusted third parties

We will never sell or share your personal data to any third party unlawfully.   
We may share your personal data with trusted third party service providers as necessary for them to perform services on our behalf, such as: 

  * Communicating with you, such as by way of email or SMS text message
  * Customer relationship management
  * Website analytics

We only share your personal data as necessary for any third party to provide the services as requested or as needed on our behalf. These third parties (and any subcontractors) are subject to strict data processing terms and conditions and are prohibited from utilising, sharing or retaining your personal data for any purpose other than as they have been specifically contracted for (or without your consent). 

**Legal compliance:**   
Pizza GoGo may disclose your personal information to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process; to comply with legal, regulatory, or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; to protect and defend Company, its subsidiaries and affiliates, and their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim, or dispute; to enforce the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website; to prevent imminent physical harm; and in the event that we find that your actions on the Website violate any laws, our Terms and Conditions of Use, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

## How do we store your data, and for how long?

We have implemented security measures to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control and will ensure to safeguard this information at all times. We do not share your data with any third party companies, except as outlined in this document. We will retain your data for a period of 36 months since your last order, unless you request otherwise. 

We store your data to allow you to place further orders more efficiently, but to also be able to recall the information should there be a problem with your order. You can request for this information to be deleted at any time, and we will do so within 30 days. Should you wish to order again in the future, then this information will need to be provided once again. 

Pizza GoGo is based in the United Kingdom and operates server infrastructure in the United Kingdom. No matter where you are located you consent to the processing and transferring of your information in the UK/EU. We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal data we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilisation of encryption where appropriate. 

If you utilise our Services from a country other than the country where our servers are located, your communications with us may result in transferring your personal data across international borders. 

**Third-party hosting:**   
We contract with a third party to maintain and host the Website and the Services. Therefore, any information you submit, including personal information, will be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by this third-party host. The third party has agreed to implement technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. 

## Understanding your rights: Access, update, or delete your data

Your data belongs to you, and we want you to be in full control of what happens to your data. We have tried to make it very easy for you to opt-in and out of any service whenever you wish by logging into your Pizza GoGo online account. Within your account you will find simple tick boxes where you can opt-in or out of each of our contact methods individually or all of them. You can also contact our data protection officer by emailing data@pizzagogo.net and putting any request in writing. We will complete your request within 30 days. 

You can update most of your data by accessing your Account Settings. You can also unsubscribe from certain emails by clicking the unsubscribe link they contain, or by visiting Communication Settings under your Account Settings. 

You may **close your account** at any time and for any reason by sending an email to data@pizzagogo.net.  
**To access, update, or delete your data** you must do a submit a data access request. Do so directly by Emailing us at data@pizzagogo.net, with the subject "Personal Data Request". We will then start the process within 30 days.  
**Object or restrict** the processing of your data by contacting us at data@pizzagogo.net. 

If you make a request to delete your personal data and that data is necessary for the products or Services you have purchased, the request will be honoured only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements. 

## Raising a complaint

You have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority. We would be grateful if you could please contact us first - we will do our very best to resolve your concern. 

Should you feel that your requests to us have not been fulfilled, you can lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO). You can find their contact details by visiting https://ico.org.uk 

## Unsolicited information

In the event you provide us with ideas or suggestions for new or existing products or services, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information") they will be deemed non-confidential and we shall be free to act on, reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution. 

## Links to other websites

Pizza GoGo may provide links to other services, in this case, Pizza GoGo is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these services.   
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by us (the "Third Party Sites"). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies. 

## Changes to this privacy policy

We aim to keep our Privacy Policy up-to-date at all times. This privacy policy was last updated May 2018.   
Although most changes are likely to be minor, We may change this policy from time to time, and at Our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## Age restrictions

Our Services are available for purchase only for those over the age of 13. Our Services are not targeted to, intended to be consumed by, or designed to entice individuals under the age of 13. If you know of or have reason to believe anyone under the age of 13 has provided us with any personal data, please contact us. 

## Trademarks and Copyright

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, button icons, images and software, is the property of Pizza GoGo Limited and is protected by UK and European copyright laws. The content and software on this site may be used as either or both of an informational or shopping resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance of the content on this site is strictly prohibited. 

## Contacting us

Email us at data@pizzagogo.net

Head Office Address:  
Unit 6, Teakcroft  
Fairview Industrial Park  
Marsh Way  
Rainham, Essex  
RM13 8UH  
United Kingdom  
Tel: 01708 551414 - Fax: 01708 553689  
Open between 10.00am and 6.00pm, Monday to Friday.
